<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Bitcoin Report</title><link>https://4855062503.github.io/bitcoin-report/</link><description>Recent content on Bitcoin Report</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://4855062503.github.io/bitcoin-report/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Lightning Betting: Identifying Our Competition</title><link>https://4855062503.github.io/bitcoin-report/posts/22-04-22/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://4855062503.github.io/bitcoin-report/posts/22-04-22/</guid><description>Below are potential competitors in the LN gamification space:
Name Category Decentralized BetPlay.io Casino No Thunderpick Casino No THNDR ESports Betting No SuredBits Sports Betting Yes BitcoinDayTrader.nl Price Betting No BetPlay BetPlay offered an easy Non-KYC way to play casino games on LN.
Their minimum LN deposit was $0.20USD, their unit of account for all games being in USD.</description></item><item><title>Bitcoin 2022 Conference Notes</title><link>https://4855062503.github.io/bitcoin-report/posts/18-04-22/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://4855062503.github.io/bitcoin-report/posts/18-04-22/</guid><description>Here are some takeaways from Bitcoin 2022: Stablecoins and confidential transactions are coming to lightning network via taproot thanks to Lightning Labs (t. Olaoluwa Osuntokun) CBDCs in US will not be similar to the digital Yuan but will be more privatized and there won&amp;rsquo;t be a single Fed Coin (t. Cynthia Lummis). The White House has had an overall positive reaction to Bitcoin&amp;rsquo;s remittance usage when being sent to Ukraine as donations (t.</description></item><item><title>New RBF Proposal</title><link>https://4855062503.github.io/bitcoin-report/posts/20-03-22/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://4855062503.github.io/bitcoin-report/posts/20-03-22/</guid><description>From the recent Core Dev meeting, there were talks of changing the RBF policy to add a limit to the amount of descendant transactions which could be allowed in the mempool. This could help in stopping pinning attacks which incrementally cause the bumping of transaction fees by attempted spends on unconfirmed transaction outputs.</description></item><item><title>Lightning Escrow</title><link>https://4855062503.github.io/bitcoin-report/posts/13-03-22/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://4855062503.github.io/bitcoin-report/posts/13-03-22/</guid><description>This service acts as a routing node between Alice and Bob, and sends to Bob from Alice if and only if Alice claims she recieved the goods that Bob promised to send.
Advantages:
Typical escrow services which involve international transfers are slow (5 days +) and costly Real estate escrows eat up major fees (sometimes 5%) Not all escrow services are programmtic, so involve more central oversight which can be exploited</description></item><item><title>Blockstream Mining Node ($BMN)</title><link>https://4855062503.github.io/bitcoin-report/posts/06-03-22/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://4855062503.github.io/bitcoin-report/posts/06-03-22/</guid><description>BMN is a securitized Bitcoin Mining Node which has an expected lifespan of 3 years.
Adam Back, CEO of Blockstream suggests that owning BMN has various benefits over just dollar-cost-averaging in Bitcoin.
These advantages are:
$BMN is registered as a security so it can offer collateral on bank loans or mortgages The energy for mining is prepaid for already, so no BTC will be sold at bearish prices during dips to pay for the energy BTC price tends to lag behind hashrate, so during difficulty drops, BTC will be mined in larger quanitites than it could have been bought The Bitcoin is HODL&amp;rsquo;d by Blockstream until the 3 year life span, only the $BMN token can be sold on the secondary-market, so no BTC will be sold at a loss</description></item><item><title>Lot49</title><link>https://4855062503.github.io/bitcoin-report/posts/27-02-22/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://4855062503.github.io/bitcoin-report/posts/27-02-22/</guid><description>Lot49 is a lightning-network protocol developed by Global Mesh Labs which incentivizes the usage of Bitcoin for off-grid communication via mesh networks
In simple terms: If Alice wants to communicate to Bob, she can communicate to Alex, who is between her and Bob, who will take a routing fee in Bitcoin via Lightning to forward her message to Bob.
Global Mesh Labs has developed GoTenna, a mesh network device.</description></item></channel></rss>